Kai Jones

Las Vegas, Nevada 89178 702-403-7823 kvjones4@cox.net

08/14/2021

To Whom it may concern

I am applying for the position of IT Support Specialist for your company, as advertised on your website. I am very keen to put my Information technology skills to effectively manage your office's operations. Having broadly researched your company's values and products, I was particularly interested in a career with your company. I am positive that your company would be the perfect place for me to utilize my capabilities and confidence.

As you will note from my enclosed resume, I possess a number of strengths and attributes which uniquely qualifies me for an administrative assistant position:

- Troubleshooting hardware and software over the phone and in person.
- Able to install and support Windows OS including command prompt and provide client support.
- Experience in identifying, using and connecting hardware components and devices.
- Understand networking, operating systems, mobile devices and security.
- Knowledge in troubleshooting device peripherals (input/output and display), PC hardware and software components, network issues, and mobile devices.
- Identifying and protecting against security vulnerabilities for devices and their network connections.
- Familiar in different types of network and connections including TCP/IP, WIFI, and SOHO.

I'm excited about putting my skills to use to contribute to Your company's success. I will call you after a week to follow-up and see if it is appropriate to arrange an interview. In the meantime, I can be reached at (702)403-7823

Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely yours,

Kai Jones

Attached: Resume

Kai Jones

Las Vegas, NV 702-403-7823

kvjones4@cox.net

• Seeking entry level employment in the Information Technology field where I can use my education and experience to benefit your company.

Summary

Objective

• Information Technology professional with 2 years' experience in a school setting learning all the skills needed, providing excellent customer service, problem solving and team reliability. Teachable, trainable and a fast learner.

Core Qualifications

- Google IT Professional Certification Google 2021
- Certified Network and PC Pro 2018 and 2019
- Entry level I.T Customer Support Rep able to answer questions and troubleshooting over the phone.
- Networking, operating systems, switches, routers, hubs, software, hardware, printers, and peripherals.
- Microsoft Office Word, Excel, Outlook, and Power Point
- Reliable, dependable, hardworking and honest

Professional Experience

Information Technology

- Troubleshooting hardware and software over the phone and in person.
- Able to install and support Windows OS including command prompt and provide client support.
- Experience in identifying, using and connecting hardware components and devices.
- Understand networking, operating systems, mobile devices and security.
- Knowledge in troubleshooting device peripherals (input/output and display), PC hardware and software components, network issues, and mobile devices.
- Identifying and protecting against security vulnerabilities for devices and their network connections.
- Familiar in different types of network and connections including TCP/IP, WIFI, and SOHO.

Customer Service / Fulfillment Associate

- Confer with customers by telephone or in person to provide information about products or services.
- Check to ensure that appropriate changes were made to resolve customers' problems.
- Cleaned and sanitized the restrooms and the areas assigned.
- Monitored food cases and kept temperatures at the appropriate degrees.
- Inbound and Outbound processing and sorting of FBA shipments. Working in fast environment.
- Scanning, soring, pallet wrapping and staging of the pallets.

Work History 2020 to Present Fulfillment Associate Amazon Las Vegas, NV 2018 to 2020 Front of Store Attendant Target Las Vegas, NV 2016 to 2018 Courtesy Clerk Smiths Las Vegas, NV

Education

- Liberty High School Diploma
- Computing and Information Technology Associates Degree College of Southern Nevada 2021
- Google IT Professional Certification Google 2021
- Certified PC Pro TestOut 2019
- Certified Network Pro TestOut 2018
- IC3 Digital Literacy Certiport 2018